<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sean Gilmore</title>
    <link>https://seangilmore.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sean Gilmore</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 10:41:05 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://seangilmore.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress with Docker and nginx-proxy</title>
      <link>https://seangilmore.dev/webdev/wordpress-with-docker-and-nginx-proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 10:41:05 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seangilmore.dev/webdev/wordpress-with-docker-and-nginx-proxy/</guid>
      <description>This article assumes you&amp;rsquo;re at least slightly familiar with Docker and Docker Compose. If you&amp;rsquo;re not sure of what Docker is, or you&amp;rsquo;d like to get started with Docker, I would check out the following links.
 Why Docker? Get Started with Docker  I am by no way a Docker expert, so if you see something in this article that you disagree with or you think could be improved upon, feel free to shoot me a tweet at @_sean_gilmore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rails 🚆: Getting started with Ajax forms</title>
      <link>https://seangilmore.dev/webdev/rails-getting-started-with-ajax-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seangilmore.dev/webdev/rails-getting-started-with-ajax-forms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rails Ajax form submission is a topic that is widely covered, but I&amp;rsquo;m yet to find a resource that deals with how to set up a completely custom implementation, from form submission to controller action, through to returning some response via Javascript and updating the page view dynamically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was learning about ajax form submission, I put together this document to help myself in the future. The problem I was working on at the time was to create a &amp;lsquo;hand raisers&amp;rsquo; form that would submit and update with a response from the server if the submission had been successful, or if it had issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you too can get some use from it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World 🌏</title>
      <link>https://seangilmore.dev/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 04:49:54 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seangilmore.dev/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World! This is the first blog on my new website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This site is built using &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; the static site generator, using a modified version of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/EmielH/tale-hugo&#34;&gt;Tale&lt;/a&gt; theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>